## **Arkadi Zavurov**

mrarkadi@gmail.com, 054-5715708, Git, LinkedIn

I am a junior Full-Stack web-developer, as well as a junior Software Developer. I have practical experience with C/C++, in a Linux environment, as well as practical experience with Javascript. I am a quick learner, highly motivated, "Team player" guy. More about me in my portfolio website

## **Areas of Expertise**

JavaScript	C++	MEAN stack	API Integrations	JQuery	Jasmine
AngularJS	Bots	SQL, NoSQL	Data Structures and Algorithms	Object Oriented Design	Testing and TDD

## Education

**2017**: Elevation Academy Ltd - coding bootcamp for Full-Stack Web Development. Among the topics that were covered:

- Version control (git, github)
- ❖ Front-End: HTML, CSS, Javascript, MVC Frameworks (Angular.js, React)
- ❖ Back-End: MEAN stack (mongoDB, Express.js, Node.js)

**2015-2016:** Experis Software R&D Ltd – a six months Kickstart program, which aims at allowing graduates to apply for core development positions open only for developers with 2-3 years of experience. Among the topics that were covered extensively:

- Data Structures and Algorithms
- ❖ Advanced C++, STL
- Object Oriented Design
- Networking, TCP/IP, Multitasking

**2014-2015:** M.A. in Economics, Tel Aviv University and The Hebrew University of Jerusalem, joint research program

**2009-2013:** B.A. in Economics, Tel Aviv University

Web Applications portfolio - Technologies used: MEAN stack, html, css, javascript, jQuery, git, npm

<u>vrsUs</u> (git) - A platform for artists to compete in 1 on 1 video battles: vote for your favorite videos, and be rated. The project was done during a hackathon.

<u>pineApp</u> (git) - A card memory game incorporating sound. With the future purpose of becoming also a platform for studying languages.

## Work Experience

2008-2013, 2015-2016: Private Tutor

- Preparing high-school students for the matriculation exam in Mathematics, English and Computer Sciences
- Giving private lessons as preparation for the Israeli Psychometric Test (SAT), as well as managing an online forum on the subject

2013-2014: Researcher at Lexidale - International Policy Consulting

2006: Administrative worker at Teva Pharmaceutical Industries

Languages: Hebrew: Mother tongue | English: Mother tongue | Russian: High level